Guide to the Donald Windham and Sandy Campbell Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Donald Windham and Sandy Campbell papers
1805-2010
1930-2010
YCAL MSS 424
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
42.03
(65 boxes) + 2 broadside folders
Writings, correspondence, photographs, artwork, and other papers by or relating to Donald Windham and Sandy Campbell.
Windham, Donald
Campbell, Sandy
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gifts and bequest of Donald Windham, 1989-2011.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Box 66 (audiovisual materials): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Donald Windham
Donald Windham (1920-2010) was an American novelist and memoirist. He collaborated with Tennessee Williams on the play You Touched Me! Windham was the partner of Sandy Campbell from 1943 until Campbell's death in 1988.
Sandy Campbell
Sandy Campbell was an American actor and publisher of the Stamperia Valdonega in Verona press.
Scope and Contents
Writings, correspondence, photographs, artwork, and other papers by or relating to Donald Windham and Sandy Campbell.
Arrangement
Organized into eight groupings: December 1989 Acquisition, April 1990 Acquisition, November 1991 Acquisition, May 1993 Acquisition, November 1993 Acquisition, December 1997 Acquisition, December 1999 Acquisition, and May 2011 Acquisition.
Audiovisual materials; Audiocassettes; Windham, Donald; Campbell, Sandy
- December 1989 Acquisition, 1940-1977; 0.42; (1 box)
  - Williams, Tennessee - Letters and Notes, 1940-1977
    Scope and Contents
    Includes correspondence with Donald Windham, Fred Melton, Sandy Campbell and others.
    - Detailed list of December 1989 Acquisition (Box 1)
    - Papers; includes correspondence with Donald Windham..., 1940-1977; 20 (Box 1)
    - Papers; includes correspondence with Donald Windham... clippings, programs, invitations, etc., 1940s (Box 1)
- April 1990 Acquisition, 1934-1942; 0.21; (1 box)
  - Williams, Tennessee - writings, 1934-1942
    Includes La Vie Boheme, Poems for K., and Lyric for K.
    - Detailed list of April 1990 Acquisition (Box 2)
    - Poems, prose and dramatic works: holograph and typescript, 1934-1942; 4 (Box 2)
- November 1991 Acquisition, 1947-1978; 0.21; (1 box)
  Includes letters, postcards, notes and clippings.
  - Capote, Truman, 1948-1978; 9 (Box 3)
  - Forster, E.M. (Edward Morgan), 1947-1962; 1965; 5 (Box 3)
- May 1993 Acquisition, 1941-1978; 0.42; (1 box)
  - Papers, 1941-1978
    - Detailed list of May 1993 Acquisition (Box 4)
    - "Donald's Sandy book" (Box 4)
      Contains empty folders and markers removed from June 1993 Acquisition.
    - Ackerley, J.R., 1951-1966; 7 (Box 4)
    - Braybrooke, Neville, 1971-1975; 2 (Box 4)
    - Camus, Albert, 1956-1959 (Box 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack, 1968 March 5 (Box 4)
    - Mann, Thomas, 1941-1945 (Box 4)
    - McCullers, Carson, 1948 (Box 4)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1944-1964; 3 (Box 4)
    - Nin, Anaïs (Box 4)
    - O'Neill, Carlotta, 1941-1946; 2 (Box 4)
    - Sitwell, Osbert, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Van Vechten, Carl, 1944-1964; 15 (Box 4)
    - Van Vechten, Fania Marinoff, 1964 (Box 4)
    - West, Nancy, 1968-1978 (Box 4)
    - Wilder, Isabel, 1964-1975 (Box 4)
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1949-1973 (Box 4)
  - Manuscripts, 1946-1948
    - Merrill, James, 1946-1948 (Box 4)
      Contains corrected signed typescripts of poems by James Merrill.
- November 1993 Acquisition, 1942-1989; 0.21; (1 box)
  - Empty folders and sleeves removed from November 1993 Acquisition (Box 5)
  - Greene, Graham, 1956-1988 (Box 5)
    Contains correspondence from Graham Greene and Graham Greene's secretary to Donald Windham and Sandy Campbell. Also contains correspondence from Donald Windham to Graham Greene.
  - Forster, E.M. (Edward Morgan) (Box 5)
    Contains a holograph of the E.M. Forster introduction to the book "The Warm Country" by Donald Windham.
  - Isherwood, Christopher, 1942-1962 (Box 5)
    Contains letters and postcards to Donald Windham and Sandy Campbell, as well a letter to Lincoln [Kirstein] from Christopher Isherwood. Also contains a typed copy on carbon paper of the poem "On his Queerness" by Christopher Isherwood.
  - Lee, Nell Harper, 1984-1989 (Box 5)
    Contains letters to Donald Windham and Sandy Campbell. Also contains a letter from Julie Fallowfield to Donald Windham (1984 December 4).
  - Bowles, Paul, 1974-1987 (Box 5)
    Contains letters and postcards to Donald Windham. Also contains a letter from Donald Windham to Paul Bowles, and a letter from Daniel Halpern to Donald Windham.
- December 1997 Acquisition, circa 1930-1950; 0.21; (1 box)
  Contains photographs.
  - Detailed list of December 1997 Acquisition (Box 6)
  - Campbell, Sandy, 1943 (Box 6)
  - Gide, Andre, 1932-1934 (Box 6)
  - Goyen, William, circa 1950 (Box 6)
  - Green, Julian, circa 1930 (Box 6)
  - Huxley, Aldous, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Isherwood, Christopher, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Kirstein, Lincoln, 1943 (Box 6)
  - Mann, Thomas, circa 1947 (Box 6)
  - Maugham, W. Somerset, circa 1942 (Box 6)
  - Moore, Marianne, circa 1940 (Box 6)
  - Parker, Dorothy, 1943 (Box 6)
  - Porter, Katherine Anne, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Prokosch, Frederic, 1938 (Box 6)
  - Russell, Bertrand, circa 1940 (Box 6)
  - Sitwell, Osbert, circa 1950 (Box 6)
  - Waugh, Evelyn, 1947 (Box 6)
  - Wescott, Glenway, circa 1940 (Box 6)
  - Windham, Donald, 1942 (Box 6)
- December 1999 Acquisition, 1930-1946; 0.21; (1 box)
  - George Platt Lynes - photographs, 1930-1946
    - Isherwood, Christopher, circa 1939-1946 (Box 67)
    - Kokoshka, Oskar, circa 1946 (Box 67)
    - Loy, Mina, 1930 (Box 67)
    - Maugham, W. Somerset, circa 1940 (Box 67)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne, circa 1940-1944 (Box 67)
    - Sitwell, Osbert (Box 67)
    - Windham, Donald, circa 1941-1942 (Box 67)
- May 2011 Acquisition, 1805-2010; 40.14; (58 boxes) + 2 broadsides
  - Correspondence, circa 1905-2010; Series I; 11.42; (12 boxes)
    Arrangement
    Arranged into four groupings: Alphabetical, Sandy Campbell and Donald Windham, Chronological by year, and Postcards.
    Correspondence consists of incoming and outgoing letters.
    - Alphabetical, circa 1940-2010
      - Filed correspondence
        - A, 1950s-1960s (Box 7)
        - B, 1960s-1970s; 2 (Box 7)
        - C, 1950s-1990s (Box 7)
        - G, 1950s-1990s (Box 7)
        - H-L, 1950s-1980s; 2 (Box 7)
        - M-Z, 1940s-1980s; 6 (Box 7)
      - Alphabetical by name
        - 1944 - ISBN (Box 8)
        - Ackerley, J.R., photocopies, 2 (Box 8)
        - As if...., 2 (Box 8)
          Includes correspondence with Tennessee Williams.
        - B:29 letters from Coconut Grove (Box 8)
        - Bowles, Paul (Box 8)
        - Bultman, Fritz - sketches for University of Georgia Museum of Art (Box 8)
        - Bultman, Fritz, 1940s-1980s; 2 (Box 8)
        - Cadmus, Paul, 1980s-1990s; 4 (Box 8)
          Includes other papers, clippings, typescripts, and photographs.
        - Cadmus, Paul - letters, 1941-1999; 3 (Box 8)
        - Campbell, Sandy - "B", 2 (Box 9)
          Includes printed correspondence (1974), clippings and photographs, as well as material dealing with Sandy Campbell and Tallulah Bankhead.
        - Campbell, Sandy - Twenty Nine Letters from Coconut Grove, 1974 (Box 9)
          Includes printed correspondence.
        - Campbell, Sandy - death, 1988; 3 (Box 9)
          Includes correspondence and material regarding Sandy Campbell's death.
        - Camus, Albert / André Gide, 1940s-1950s (Box 9)
        - Capote, Truman - letters, etc., 2 (Box 9)
          Includes mostly correspondence with Marie Dewey ( In Cold Blood ) and Jack Dunphy, Capote's longtime companion.
        - Clift, Montgomery, 1946-1980s; 2 (Box 9)
          Also contains correspondence from Ethel Clift.
        - Conlon, Christopher (Box 9)
        - Cornell, Joseph (Box 9)
        - Cornell, Joseph (Box 9)
          Includes material regarding the "Windham: Cornell-Ashton" manuscript.
        - Cornell, Joseph, 2 (Box 9)
        - Cornell, Joseph, 1940s-1970s; 7 (Box 10)
          Includes The Bel Canto Pet (1955) and Maria (1954).
        - Cornell, Joseph - posthumous, 1970s-1980s; 3 (Box 10)
        - de Lanux, Eyre (Box 10)
        - DeVries, Keith, 1940s-1970s (Box 10)
        - Dewey, A.A., 1970s-1980s (Box 10)
        - Dillon, Millicent, 1991 (Box 10)
        - "Doris Cartoons", 1940s (Box 10)
        - Digby, John and Joan, 2 (Box 10)
        - Fish, Doris, 1970s-1980s (Box 10)
        - Footnote to a Friendship - reponses (Box 10)
        - Footnote to a Friendship - book, photographs, etc. (Box 11)
        - Ford, 1940s-1970s (Box 11)
        - Forster, E.M., 1975 (Box 11)
        - Forster, E.M. (Box 11)
        - Forster, E.M., 1970s-1990s (Box 11)
        - French, Jared - posthumous (Box 11)
        - French, Jared and Margaret (Box 11)
        - "From Guy (and Jeff)", postcards, 1990s (Box 11)
        - Greene, Graham (Box 11)
        - Hart-Davis, Rupert (Box 11)
        - Inventory letters (Box 11)
        - Isherwood, Christopher (Box 11)
        - Kirstein, Lincoln / Isherwood (Box 11)
        - Leavitt et al (Box 11)
        - LeClercq, Tanaquil and George Balanchine (Box 11)
        - Lee, Harper (Box 11)
        - Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne, 2 (Box 11)
          Includes a copy of The Sorrows of Young Werther by Johann Wolfgang von Goethe (1949), which belonged to Lynn Fontanne.
        - Lynes, George Platt (Box 11)
        - Mann, Thomas (Box 11)
        - Mardersteig - Officina Bodoni, 1980s-1990s (Box 11)
        - Mardersteig - Stone in the Hourglass (Box 11)
        - Maxwell, William (Box 11)
        - Melton, Fred (Box 11)
        - Melton, Fred (Box 12)
        - Merrill, James (Box 12)
        - Miscellaneous letters from readers, 2 (Box 12)
        - Mrs. Joyce of Russia and Mr. Fortes of King's, 2 (Box 12)
        - New York Public Library (Box 12)
        - Parker, Peter and Christopher Porter (Box 12)
        - Plomer, William (Box 12)
        - Pound, Ezra (Box 12)
        - Purdy, James, 1950s-1980s (Box 12)
        - Rapisarda, Stefano, 1960s-1970s (Box 12)
        - Roman Spring of Alice Toklas, 2 (Box 12)
        - Schuyler, James (Box 12)
        - Simenon, Georges, 1960s-1980s (Box 12)
        - Smith, Tony and Jane Lawrence (Box 12)
        - Soldati, Mario, 2 (Box 13)
        - Stone in the Hourglass, 3 (Box 13)
        - Svendsen, Clara, 1945-1989; 3 (Box 13)
        - Szladitis, Lola L. (Box 13)
        - Tanaquil (Box 13)
        - Unfinished business (Box 13)
        - University of Georgia Press, 2 (Box 13)
        - Van Vechten, Carl - photocopies, 2 (Box 13)
        - Wescott, Glenway, 1940s-1970s (Box 14)
        - Williams, Tennessee, 5 (Box 14)
        - Wilson, Ronald, 2 (Box 14)
        - Yale University - Beinecke Library (Box 14)
        - You Touched Me, 1940s-2000s
          Correspondence and various material regarding You Touched Me, by Tennessee Williams and Donald Windham.
          - Journal entries, 1940s-1970s (Box 14)
          - Kellner, Bruce, 2000s; 2 (Box 14)
          - You Touched Me, 1945-1991; 4 (Box 14)
            Includes a copy of the You Touched Me manuscript, financial statements from 1945 to 1957, information regarding the Cleveland Playhouse (circa 1991) and correspondence from The Director's Company.
          - You Touched Me - legal (Box 15)
          - You Touched Me, 1996-2000s (Box 15)
    - Sandy Campbell and Donald Windham, 1943-1968
      - Donald Windham letters, 1943-1961; 6 (Box 16)
      - Sandy Campbell letters, 1943-1968; 7 (Box 16)
    - Chronological by year, circa 1905-2010
      - 1905-1991 (Box 17)
      - 1948-1992 (Box 17)
      - 1960s-1970s (Box 17)
      - 1960s-1995 (Box 17)
      - 1960s-2000s, 2 (Box 17)
      - 1990s, 2 (Box 17)
        Also includes Sandy Campbell obituary notices and property insurance information, circa 2006.
      - 1990s-2000s, 2 (Box 17)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 17)
        Includes material from Bruce Kellner.
      - 2000s, 4 (Box 17)
        Includes correspondence and paperwork from the Yale Art Gallery, as well as various writings.
    - Postcards (Box 18)
      Contains a collection of postcards. Some postcards have correspondence, while others are blank.
  - Writings, Drafts and Manuscripts, Series II; 4.25; (5 boxes) + 2 broadside folders
    Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - The Angelic Avengers, 2 (Box 19)
    - As If..., 3 (Box 19)
    - "Button: Henrietta" (Box 19)
    - "Capote letters and my journal entries about TC" (Box 19)
    - The Dog Star, 6 (Box 19)
    - Donald Windham, A Bio-Bibliography (Box 19)
    - Donald Windham, A Bio-Bibliography, cover (Box 20 Oversize)
    - Footnote to a Friendship, 2 (Box 19)
    - Jealousy and Zeal (Box 21)
    - The Hero Continues, 3 (Box 21)
    - Kelly Boys (Box 21)
    - Like a Flower, 2 (Box 21)
    - The Listener, issues 1562 and 1157 (Box 21)
    - The Listener, issue1566 (Box 21)
    - The Listener, issue 1581 (Box 21)
    - "Mrs. Joyce of Zurich and Mr. Forster of King's", by Sandy Campbell (Box 21)
    - "My Childhood - Walk" (Box 21)
    - "New Start" (Box 21)
    - "A Note on Pierre Herbart's 'Andre Gide' as a Portrait of the Artist" (Box 21)
    - "Posthumous Thought and Nightcaps" (Box 21)
    - "Publishing" (Box 21)
    - "The Roman Spring of Alice Toklas" (Box 21)
    - Servants with Torches, covers and title pages (Box 22 Broadside)
    - Servants with Torches, pages of story (Box 20 Oversize)
    - "The Starless Air", 6 (Box 23)
    - Stone in the Hourglass, 3 (Box 23)
    - Stone in the Hourglass, covers, some signed by Bultman (Box 24 Broadside)
    - Television scripts for MCA (Box 23)
    - Two People, 2 (Box 23)
    - View, issue 3 (Box 23)
    - Work in Progress
      - "Work in Progress", 2 (Box 23)
      - "June 26, 1988" (Box 23)
      - "St. Luke's Place", 2 (Box 23)
      - "Princeton" (Box 23)
      - "Fire Island" (Box 25)
      - "Westfield (Childhood)" (Box 25)
      - "Fort Dix", 2 (Box 25)
      - "Dear Bugger", 3 (Box 25)
      - "Single Harvest" (Box 25)
      - "Who is Dead and Who is Alive", 2 (Box 25)
    - "To Write" (Box 25)
    - "A Year Without Sleep" (Box 25)
    - "747 Madison Avenue" (Box 25)
    - Windham autobiography (Box 25)
      - "Early - 1943 & Before" (Box 25)
      - "1943" (Box 25)
      - "Spring 1944 Summer" (Box 25)
      - "1948 Italy", 5 (Box 25)
      - "1950s" (Box 25)
  - Journals, notebooks, day calendars, circa 1940-2009; Series III; 4.42; (5 boxes)
    Arranged into three groupings: Datebooks, Journals, and Miscellaneous.
    - Datebooks, 1986-2009
      Arranged chronologically.
      - Datebook, 1986 (Box 26)
      - Datebooks, 1988-1989 (Box 26)
      - Datebooks, 1990-1992 (Box 26)
      - Datebooks, 1993-1995 (Box 26)
      - Datebooks, 1996-1998 (Box 26)
      - Datebook, 1999 (Box 26)
      - Datebooks, 2000-2001 (Box 26)
      - Datebook, 2002 (Box 26)
      - Datebook, 2003 (Box 26)
      - Datebooks, 2004-2005 (Box 26)
      - Datebooks, 2006-2007 (Box 26)
      - Datebooks, 2008-2009 (Box 26)
    - Journals, 1942-2002
      - Journal, 1942-1943 (Box 26)
      - Journal, 1943-1949 (Box 26)
      - Journal, 1946 July-August (Box 26)
      - Journal, 1948-1951 (Box 27)
      - Journal, 1949-1950 (Box 27)
      - Journal, 1951-1952 (Box 27)
      - Journal, 1953 (Box 27)
      - Journal, 1954 (Box 27)
      - Journal, 1955-1956 (Box 27)
      - Journal, circa 1956 (Box 27)
      - Journal, 1958-1959 (Box 27)
      - Journal, 1960-1963 (Box 27)
      - Journal, circa 1964 (Box 27)
      - Journal, 1964-1974 (Box 27)
      - Journal, 1973-1975 (Box 28)
      - Journal, 1976-1978 (Box 28)
      - Journal, 1979-1983 (Box 28)
      - Journal, 1983-1989 (Box 28)
      - Journal, 1989-1992 (Box 28)
      - Journal, 1992-1997 (Box 28)
      - Journal, 1997-2002 (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous
      - B notebooks, 1940s-1950s (Box 28)
      - Typed notebooks, 1941-1943 (Box 28)
      - 3 small notebooks, circa 1950-1959 (Box 28)
      - Italian date and address books, 1950s-1960s (Box 29)
      - Typed journal, 1951-1955 (Box 29)
      - Typed journal, 1956-1959 (Box 29)
      - Notebook - Italian vocabulary (Box 29)
      - Notebooks and Italian wordbook (Box 29)
      - Sandy Campbell journals, 1957-1980; 2 (Box 30)
      - Diary calendars, 1962-1987; 8 (Box 30)
  - Photographs, circa 1895-1999; Series IV; 7.08; (8 boxes)
    Arranged into two groupings: General photographs and Living Room photographs.
    - General photographs, 1920-1999
      Files are not arranged in any particular order.
      - Donald Windham, Sandy Campbell, 1971 (Box 31)
      - Scrapbook - Donald Windham, Sandy Campbell, Paul Cadmus, 1970 (Box 31)
      - Italy - Don, Sandy, 1965 (Box 31)
      - Scrapbook - New York, Italy - Donald Windham, Sandy Campbell, 1966-1967 (Box 31)
      - Scrapbook, 1968-1969 (Box 31)
      - Scrapbook, 1969 (Box 31)
      - Scrapbook, 1968 (Box 31)
      - Scrapbook, 1969-1970 (Box 31)
      - Album, 1956 (Box 31)
      - Album - Paul Cadmus, Jared French, Donald Windham, Sandy Campbell (Box 31)
      - Album, 1950 (Box 31)
      - Album, 1960s-1970s (Box 31)
      - Album (Box 31)
      - Album, 1940s (Box 31)
      - Photo album, 1946-1947 (Box 32)
      - Photo album, 1948 (Box 32)
      - Photo album, 1949-1954 (Box 32)
      - Photo album, 1958-1959 (Box 32)
      - Photo album, 1956-1957 (Box 32)
      - Photo albums, 1960 (Box 32)
      - Photo albums, 1961 (Box 32)
      - Photo albums, 1962-1964 (Box 32)
      - Carl Van Vechten postcard, 1955 (Box 32)
        Postcard is a Carl Van Vechten photograph of Marlon Brando, taken during the run of Streetcar Named Desire, 1948
      - Album, 1940s-1990s (Box 32)
      - Italy, Fire Island - Paul Cadmus et alia (Box 32)
      - Prints, contact prints, negatives - London, Cambridge, 1960, 1969 (Box 32)
      - Negatives - Rome, Sicily, New York, 1966-1967 (Box 32)
      - Photographs, negatives - Fire Island; "Air February 1950" Magazine, 1978 (Box 32)
      - "Photos of Don" - various locations, 1920-1977 (Box 32)
        Includes photographs with Tennessee Williams and John Digby.
      - "The Homeplace," Atl., GA; Tennessee Williams letters; "Happy New Year" Mouse Doodle, circa 1987 (Box 33)
      - Digby opening in Brooklyn, 1981 (Box 33)
      - Envelope [empty] - Leddick to Windham (Box 33)
      - Photographs and negatives - Rome, boat trip - D. Windham and Sandy Campbell, 1961 (Box 33)
      - Photographs and negatives - various locations - Capote negatives, 1946-1958 (Box 33)
      - Photographs and negatives - NYC, Mexico, Cuba - Easter card 4/23/00, 1947-1987 (Box 33)
      - Photo album - "Donald Windham and Sandy Campbell", 1940s-1960s; 7 (Box 33)
        Includes photographs, clippings, art by "Lenard," and Renaissance art.
      - Photo album - "Donald Windham and Sandy Campbell", 1940s-1960s (Box 34 Oversize)
        Includes photographs, clippings, art by "Lenard," and Renaissance Art.
      - Photo albums - "Various", 1940s-1960s (Box 34 Oversize)
        Includes Montgomery Clift material, photographs of Donald Windham, contact prints, a print of Paul Cadmus' "Reflections" and photographs of Sandy Campbell.
      - "Various Photographs of Sandy Campbell" (Box 34 Oversize)
        Includes a photograph of a Paul Cadmus portrait of Sandy Campbell, circa 1943.
      - "Photos of Sandy's Book in Gotham" (Box 33)
      - Negatives and contact prints, 1960-1962 (Box 33)
        Includes New York, Provincetown and England material.
      - Negatives - Europe, 1965 (Box 33)
      - Negatives - "Fire Island", 1971-1972 (Box 33)
      - Negatives - "Europe", 1960 (Box 33)
      - Photographs and negatives, circa 1987 (Box 33)
      - Various photographs of Donald Windham and Others, 1950s-1980s (Box 33)
        Includes Donald Windham in Athens, 1960; Donald Windham in "17B," 1979; prints of Truman Capote, late 1950s; Donald Windham & Tanaquil LeClercq.
      - Dragon - prints, 1960 (Box 33)
      - Negatives - various, 1960s (Box 33)
      - Mexico, 1956 (Box 33)
      - "Europe Duplicates", 1948 (Box 33)
      - Prints - "Italy, Scotland and Fire Island", 1970 (Box 35)
      - Prints - "Europe Duplicates", 1948 (Box 35)
      - Prints - "Greece/Venice 1960" (Box 35)
      - "NYC, Cabris, Pine Mt. Rd., Italy 1950", 1950s-1960s (Box 35)
        Includes In Cold Blood photographs; negative rolls
      - Personal - "Bad 1960" - slides (Box 35)
      - Personal - "NYC Dec. '59, Good" - slides, 1959; 2 (Box 35)
      - Various negatives, 1950s-1960s (Box 35)
        Includes Sicily 1950; New York City 1960; New York Central Park, 80th St. apartment.
      - Kodak Ektra camera with leather case and Kodak camera neck strap (Box 36)
      - "Paris, Italy - 1948" - negatives, circa 1948-1950 (Box 36)
      - Sandy Campbell family photographs (Box 36)
      - "Photos of Sandy [Campbell's] Books in Gotham Window", circa 1988 (Box 36)
      - "Valentine [Fritz's]" photograph (Box 36)
      - Photo album - "Sandy Campbell" - photographs (Box 36)
        Includes photographs Taken in Paul Cadmus's Studio for "Reflection," 1944.
      - Photographs and negatives - Italy 1970, Rome and Venice 1968, Ship 1971, photographs of Don & Tennessee, circa 1968-1971 (Box 36)
      - Photographs and negatives - Rome, Venice1983, Tobago 1984, Europe 1965, Italy 1948, Europe 1968, misc., circa 1948-1984 (Box 36)
        Includes photographs of Tennessee Williams and Truman Capote.
      - Photographs and negatives - Rome 1965, Spin-Italy 1969, Eyre's 1968, misc., circa 1965-1969 (Box 36)
        Includes photographs of Tennessee Williams and Eugene May.
      - Photographs and negatives - many locations, 1960-1972 (Box 36)
        Includes photographs of Tennessee Williams and E.M. Forster.
      - Photographs and negatives - Fire Island 1990, postcards, Tennessee Williams Letter, Stefano Rapisarda photographs (Box 36)
      - Cards and postcards, 1963-1972 (Box 36)
      - Photographs and negatives - Jeanne Bultman, J.D. Ackley, et al. - Misc. cards and postcards (Box 37)
      - Photographs and negatives, circa 1948-1976 (Box 37)
      - Card, family photographs, misc. photographs, artwork (Box 37)
        Includes Paul Cadmus, George Tooker, and Jared French.
      - Photographs of artwork, photographs previously held by Don's mother (Box 37)
        Includes Paul Cadmus artwork.
      - Photographs and negatives - Verona 1964, Rome/Italy 1967, Windham sketches, 1960s (Box 37)
      - Journal with erotic clippings and photographs (Box 37)
      - NYC Ballet programs, erotic photographs and artwork, nude and misc. photographs, Jane Lawrence Smith photographs (Box 37)
      - Family photographs 1937-1940, portraits 1979; postcards to Louise Windham 1946-1971 (Box 37)
      - Photographs by Fred Melton, misc. photographs, portrait sketch (Box 37)
      - Photographs - Jamaica 1946, New York 1954, 1957 (Box 37)
      - Norway and Denmark 1972, Spain and Italy 1968, London, New York circa 1950, Tripoli 1960, West Indies 1969, circa 1950-1972 (Box 37)
        Includes photographs of Truman Capote.
      - Display of Tennessee Williams and Donald Windham work, Atlanta photography, Tammy, George B., Diana Adams (Box 37)
    - Living Room photographs, 1895-1985
      Arranged in a rough alphabetical order.
      - Ackerley, J.R. and Queenie (dog) (Box 38)
      - Balanchine, George, Nick Magallanes and Marie Jeanne., 1940s (Box 38)
        Photograph by George Platt Lynes.
      - Bankhead, Tallulah and Winston Churchill (lion) (Box 38)
        Postcard by Carl Van Vechten.
      - Blixen, Karen (Tania) (Box 38)
      - Blixen, Karen (Tania) (Box 38)
      - Brandon, Peter - New York City, 1958 (Box 38)
      - Capote, Truman, 1961 (Box 38)
      - Capote, Truman, Harper Lee and unknown man with child (Box 38)